I'm so excited to have been one of the
six that started the Journey of
Prudential in Uganda
it's remarkable to have started with a
market share of only 0.4 percent in 2015
to the current 27.4
which is further solidifying our
position as the leading life and health
insurer in Uganda it's been an adventure
watching producer Uganda grow and evolve
as we celebrate this incredible
Milestone I'm filled with pride and
gratitude for being part of prudentials
growth journey in Africa
here's to many more Amazing years ahead
I have been privileged to embark on an
incredible journey with nursing the
growth of Prudential in Uganda from the
beginning we have laid a foundation and
carelessly walked towards the growth of
a robust system within Venture we are
committed to serve our customers and our
agency Force we have improved so much
into the systems that we have built we
have adopted to Cloud Technologies and
we have adopted to different ways of
working from the humble beginnings of
Prudential in Uganda
have been fortunate enough to witness
every step of our remarkable Journey we
studied as a tiny seed and blossomed
into the number one life insurance
provider in the country
none of this would have been possible
without the incredible team whose
dedication and passion has propelled us
to Great midst here is to the journey
and the growth of Prudential reflecting
back to 2015 when Prudential first
opened its doors in Uganda it was
a future that was blurry but we were
sold to a dream that would achieve a lot
of success in terms of career with
Prudential so seeing how far that has
brought me today I would say it's been a
blessing and I'm forever grateful to the
people that sold to me the dream of
Prudential because it has given me an
opportunity to grow from being an agent
to a team leader to a supervisor to a
manager currently to an agency director
which has been a wonderful journey and
plus personal achievements in terms of
production such as mgrity two times and
then the President's Cup qualification
has given me exposure to meet the
biggest players in in Prudential happy
anniversary Prudential happy anniversary
Prudential happy anniversary prediction
it has been a wonderful experience hello
everyone it's time to celebrate a
Monumental Milestone as Prudential tense
175 years
now this incredible journey holds
immense significance for us and most
importantly for our cherished clients
and Prospects since our establishment in
Uganda in 2015 we've been dedicated to
building trust securing Futures and
being your go-to life and health
insurance provider
so let's raise a tools to the next 175
years of providing unwavering health and
financial protection for you our clients
thank you for being part of prudential's
remarkable story
happy anniversary to us all let's face
life together
thank you for working this journey with
us
celebration life happy
175. let's face life together